Kieran Halliday

Bachelor of Applied Science in Computer Engineering, Minor in Commerce

Personal Info

E-mail

kieran.halliday@pm.me

GitHub

kieranhalliday

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kieranhalliday-7bb359116/

Skills

Software Development

Skilled in: Java, C++, Python

CI/CD

Teamcity, automation, bash scripting

Awards

2018

B.C. Technology Award

2018

Archie Bruce Memorial Scholarship

2017

A.H. Younger Memorial Scholarship in Engineering

2017

Richard Genest Memorial Service Award

Languages

French

DELF B2 Certification

Summary

Senior computer engineering student with 18 months work experience in mobile development. Acheived Academic All American status and Dean's List honours while competing as a varsity track athlete. Can manage difficult workloads under short time constraints. Contributed to open source projects.

Experience

2018-05 - Software Engineering Intern

CA Technologies

2018-08

Agrifac B.V.

- Designed and implemented new console on supply station
- Worked in multi-language environment including C++, C#, and five IEC supported PLC languages
- Managed project's automated testing and nightly builds

2017-09 - Software Engineering Co-op - Mobile Team

2018-05

- Improved Android automated test suite coverage by over 50%

- Created 12 new nightly automation build configurations
- Helped reduce release time from six months to two weeks
- Added SDK support for new platform (Xamarin)

2017-05 - Assistant Systems Administrator

2017-09

Yukon Department of Economic Development

- Primary contact for most hardware and software issues
- Solving new problems as a daily basis
- Managed and updated department's physical resources

Education

2014-09 - University of British Columbia

2019-05

- Expected graduation May 2019
- Breadth of courses ranges from operating systems and hardware development to upper year art history and creative writing
- Academic All-American in the NAIA

Technical Projects

2017-09 - Volunteer App Development

present Run for Life

- Created Android and iOS app to facilitate water data collection in Kenya
- Sponsored by Run for Life in order to find potential well sites near local schools
- App was presented to the Canadian High Commissioner in Nairobi in January 2018